(Sheldon:)...to be the lower-left corner
on Hollywood Squares.
(Sheldon:)Oh, damn! The floppy failed.
(Sheldon:)Well, whoever was in charge
of quality control...
(Sheldon:)...at the Verbatim Corporation in 1989,
congratulations, you just made the list.
- Howard?
- Change your mind about sex?
(Howard:)I'm still mad but I'll do it.
(Bernadette:)No, I've just been thinking.
(Bernadette:)It doesn't matter
if I'm afraid for your safety.
(Bernadette:)I don't want to be the person who stands
between you and your dreams.
- Really?
- Really.
(Bernadette:)If going into space means that much
I will never say another word about it.
Thank you, heh.
(Bernadette:)- I love you.
- I love you too, heh.
(Howard:)So sex now?
(Sheldon:)- Okay.
- Heh.
(Bernadette:)I just forgot to brush my teeth.
I'll be right back.